Inaban...
I thought you were going to die!
Like I'd die from standing up too fast.
I was really scared.
I thought he might have done something.
Balloon Vine didn't do anything.
I just haven't been feeling well lately.
I don't think it's something I need to be in the infirmary for.
Enough, Inaba-chan.
You have to take care of your own body.
You're lecturing me?
I'm being serious here.
Sure. Whatever.
You're blowing this out of proportion.
I can make it home just fine by myself.
Kiriyama would kill me tomorrow if I let you go alone.
Right?
Especially since Yui and Aoki wanted to come too.
Yeah, that's not happening.
The last thing I need is the four of you dragging me around.
Speaking of which, Taichi...
It's about time you told us what happened between you and Yui yesterday.
What do you mean, "speaking of which"?
That didn't follow at all.
Who cares if it follows?
If you don't tell me,
I might faint again out of curiosity.
Threatening me with your health isn't fair!
I just might faint out of shock.
It's almost like you can't trust us.
Right, Inaban?
Yeah.
Okay, okay.
But there are a few parts I can't tell you about.
How you even got that idea is beyond me,
selfless freak!
You don't have to laugh so hard.
So, does it still hurt down there?
Oh, shut up.
Nagase, help me out here.
What's wrong?
I hadn't noticed at all.
I knew Yui felt uncomfortable around men,
but I had no idea she was so afraid of them.
Nagase, I don't think Kiriyama wants anyone to treat her differently
or feel uncomfortable around her.
So just treat her the same as you always have.
The same as I always have?
Is that really okay?
Yeah.
More than okay.
You two are a perfect match.
You need each other.
That's clear as day.
Inaban!
Can you stop analyzing us like that?
Like how you said Taichi and I were...
"hi-ho, the derry-o" or something!
But you really are "hi-ho, the derry-o."
And you know, Yui might be falling for Taichi too.
Wh-What?
Inaban, not in front of him.
The problem with selfless freaks is that everyone starts falling for them.
Don't forget that kindness can hurt people too.
I'll... keep that in mind.
Sorry for all the trouble.
Forget about it.
Just get some rest.
Inaban, you should be worried about your body right now, not about us.
I'll be fine.
Oh, right.
I almost forgot.
Iori,
have Taichi help you with your trauma too.
Inaban, you promised not to tell anyone.
Taichi, I know you can do it.
So do it.
Inaban's being presumptuous.
Too presumptuous.
I know she's just thinking about what's best for me, but...
Do you want to know, Taichi? About my past.
Well...
If you promise to treat me the same as you always have, I'll tell you.
Okay. I promise.
I knew you'd say that.
Okay, guess I'll start.
But first...
I think I'll tell a joke.
I thought it'd be a good idea to tell a joke before moving on to something more serious.
You don't need to. Why would you even think that?
But it's times like these when I can't think of a joke!
Then why bother trying?
Just kidding.
The joke was that I thought I'd tell a joke when I didn't have one.
But it's not that I actually didn't have a joke.
I just decided that the joke would be that I didn't have one.
I hope you get it.
Why hope for something like that?!
The fact that you don't need to joke is more important
than your joke about not having a joke to begin with!
Taichi, you're so easy to bait.
I can't seem to help myself when I'm around you.
You see...
I have five dads.
But legally, I guess it's only three.
You mean your mom divorced and remarried that many times?
Yup.
And there were a few problems with my second dad.
Honestly, he was a pretty violent person.
But it wasn't really that serious.
Or rather, I never let it get that serious.
I pretended to be a different "me,"
and became who he wanted me to be.
What do you—
I did whatever it took to make sure he didn't get mad.
As long as I kept that up, he was satisfied.
Sometimes he'd even pat me on the back.
I even changed my tastes to match his.
I think this was back in first grade.
I've been pretending to be different "me's" ever since.
But last spring, when my fifth father was on his deathbed, he told me,
"You should live the way you want."
After he died, my mom cried and said, "I'm so sorry I never thought about what you wanted.
I'll do everything I can so we can live the way you want from now on."
And we lived happily ever after.
So you're getting along with your mom?
But then the worst epilogue imaginable followed.
To live the way I want...
I don't know how to do that.
What did I like?
What did I want to do?
Having spent most of my life pretending and living for someone else,
I eventually forgot who I really was.
I can't do what I want
if I don't know what I want to do.
So I decided to choose a personality that would fit the given situation.
Ironically,
the only thing I know for sure about myself is that I can tell exactly what someone else wants.
But even that's starting to fade.
I didn't realize Yui was so afraid of men.
But—
Then we started switching personalities.
I've already lost most of my own personality.
And when we switch bodies, it's like I lose whatever little remains.
Eventually, no one will realize that it's me.
Even I won't be able to tell.
And before long, I'll fade away, just like that.
I won't let that happen!
Because...
no matter what happens...
no matter who you pretend to be...
I'll always know who you are.
That's impossible.
It's not impossible.
How can you be so sure?
That's because...
I love...
Selfless freak.
A-Anyway, I know I can do it.
Just trust me.
Okay.
If you say you can, I guess I'll trust you.
Morning, Taichi.
M-Morning, Nagase.
You'll treat me the same, no matter what I tell you.
That was our promise to each other as men.
Who are you supposed to be?
You'll treat me the same, no matter what I tell you.
That was our promise to each other as men!
Why'd you say it again?
And you're not a man.
I wonder why things feel so passionate just by adding "as men" to it.
Like I'd know.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yeah! Never better!
But the person you should really be worrying about is...
I'm guessing it's Taichi in my body.
Taichi!
Taichi, are you okay?
Seriously, learn to hold it in.
Get some guts.
I think your guts are the problem here.
Iori, go back to class.
What about you two?
I'll put that thing to bed.
Don't worry. I won't push my own body too hard.
We're back?
Yeah.
You can go back to class now.
Like I could leave you here looking like that.
Sorry.
It's okay.
You've been acting really weird lately.
Didn't I say that I'm okay?
You definitely don't look it.
If there's a reason, tell me.
Shut up already. My head hurts.
Inaba!
I want to help you!
Why do you want to help me?
Because—
Don't say "I just want to" or "we're friends."
Because you're always looking out for us.
Whenever something happens—
So you wouldn't help me if I weren't useful to you?
That's not what I meant.
Isn't saying it that way kind of unfair?
It's not unfair.
Why do you all have to be so nice?
If only you were darker on the inside...
"Darker"?
No, that's not right.
I'm the one who needs to change.
Inaba, are you sure you're okay?
What are you worried about?
My body will feel better in no time.
I'm not talking about your body.
I'm not okay.
Wait.
I didn't say that.
Forget I did.
You...
When I said "I'm not okay," I meant—
You told me that this whole thing is a disaster.
Are you sure you're not the one suffering the most from it?
I am completely out of it today,
showing weakness to an enemy.
You said something like that before.
Inaba...
Am I your enemy?
No!
That's not what I meant!
You guys are...
the best friends I could ever ask for.
And that makes you my worst enemies.
What does—
That's all I have to say.
Just go back to class.
You can't call me a friend if you're suffering this much and can't tell me why.
Then let me be perfectly clear.
I can't trust any of you.
When we switch bodies, whatever someone does, crime or otherwise,
the responsibility falls on the body's original owner.
You're basically free to do as you please.
You think we'd do something like that?
Crimes might be going too far,
but it's not like you couldn't steal a few coins every time.
That might be true, but...
I always imagine that you might do things like that.
It scares me so much that I can't sleep at night.
And more than anything else,
I hate myself for being able to imagine things like that.
You, Iori, Yui, and Aoki—
you all really trust each other.
I'm the only one worrying about things like this.
Inaba, we wouldn't hate you just because—
But after hearing something like this, we can't go back to the way we were.
Taichi,
I don't trust anyone in this world.
So everyone is my enemy.
And out of everyone, you're probably my worst enemy.
Because unless I'm mistaken,
you trust me more than anybody.
Sometimes I think that I could have as much fun as everyone else if I could just trust someone.
But because I can't commit, I find myself suffering every day.
I don't have any trauma like Iori or Yui.
You always see people with personalities they don't like because something tragic happened to them.
In my opinion, that's a good thing.
They just need to get over their trauma.
But what about someone who doesn't have any trauma?
Being distrustful of others is how I've been since I was born,
so the only way to change that is to stop being "me."
To stop being "me"...
In that sense, there's no saving you from your selflessness.
Weren't you born that way too?
I guess.
I suppose you can't save someone who doesn't have any trauma.
But isn't that because they don't need to be saved?
If that's the way you were born, it's probably not a big deal.
So basically, I'm stupid for even worrying about this?
I didn't say that.
But it might be that way if you reason it out.
Taichi—
But that part of you is fine by me.
What?
I'm sad you'll never be able to trust me,
but you don't need to change yourself because of that.
We can accept you like that.
Nagase, Kiriyama, Aoki,
and me.
Are you stupid?!
It can't be that easy!
We can't say that for sure.
So why not tell them?
Just like you told me.
You think I could do something so risky?!
What if they don't accept—
If that happens,
you still have me.
Either way, first, you need to accept yourself.
That's what I think.
But I just can't.
No matter what I do, I can't see it ending well.
Hey, Inaba...
I think that by believing you can't let anyone else know about something,
that something seems a lot worse than it actually is.
So I'll tell you a secret that I thought I'd carry with me to the grave.
What do you mean?
You'll tell me your secret, so I'll tell them mine?
That's right.
If anyone finds out about this,
my high school life will be over.
I'd probably die socially.
That's how dangerous it is.
What is wrong with you?
Inaba, k-keep it down.
Then why don't you tell me this "secret" of yours?
I'll decide what to do after I hear it.
Then... here I go...
I've...
I've masturbated to you before!
By "masturbate," do you mean that...
Yeah.
So you've probably... to Iori and Yui too?
I see.
Just for the record, I don't do it every day!
Actually, I rarely do it at all.
Are you listening to me?
Pervert!
You pervert!
Wanker! Jerk-off! Sicko! Freak! Creep!
But that part of you is fine by me.
Man, everything is just so stupid.
Confessing that you did something like that is stupid.
Thinking that you could convince me with it is stupid.
And thinking that you'd come out fine after telling me is stupid.
And more than anything, actually feeling moved by it is stupid.
Need a tissue?
Dammit, what is wrong with you?
Are you trying to make me fall for you too?
And that's how it is.
Inaban,
you mean...
you're a worrywart?
W-Worrywart?
It's not that sim—
I know how you feel!
I check my body whenever I switch with Aoki.
What?
Then I make sure he hasn't taken anything I own.
That hurts!
That really hurts, you know!
Wait, is it only for me?
What about Taichi?
Um... Is that all you have to say about this?
To be honest, you are overthinking things.
Like with the crimes and stuff.
But don't worry.
I won't do anything bad in your body.
Wait, Inaba-chan!
You don't trust anyone, right?
It's not just me?
Is that all you care about?!
For now, let's just have lunch.
Break's going to be over soon.
Good idea. We can talk about this over lunch.
Why the heck was I worried over all this?
Now I feel like an idiot.
I haven't done anything bad in your body!
Well, at least I got a juicy secret out of you.
I can't trust you.
Inaba, do you think you could forget—
Weren't you making weird movies with Taichi the other day?
Nope.
That was just one time!
Instead, I'll tell you one of my secrets.
Oh, so you did!
What weird movies?!
When was this?!
Then we'll be in the same boat.
I've masturbated to you too.
...but you're crazy in a nice way.
I'm in love with you. That hasn't changed.
Taichi, how do you feel about Iori?
You're nothing but a selfish freak!
Well, sorry!
Nagase!